E-learnings are extremely useful
They speed up your onboarding,
can distribute a lot of information over
a great amount of people for a low price
and can easily streamline trainings
for large amounts of employees.
Though, they often fall short.
Nobody finishes them,
They are not interesting
for the target audience,
Or they merely get deployed
to push large amounts of information
to your target audience
instead of involving
the audience.
That’s where we come in.
I’m Django van den Busken from 24Film.
I’m film director and producer,
and specialize in
creating e-learning videos.
My background as a teacher,
my experience teaching film courses and acting classes,
and my knowledge of views,
retention and clickthrough rates,
give me the tools necessary
to solve these problems.
We work from our ‘Retention First’ Model,
where viewer attention is essential
for a good e-learning.
In this series I want to show you
the process of how an e-learning is created,
so that, by the end, you know
why our e-learnings stick around.